http://www.icestore.com/privacy.asp

Privacy
Your information is safe.
The IceStore website (the
"website") is operated by IceStore, LLC ("Company").
Your privacy is very important to us. We do not sell or otherwise provide your
personal information to third parties for any reason, except as required by
law. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we
use and protect your personal information.
In this Privacy Policy we provide detailed information on when and why we
collect your personal information, how we use it, and how we keep it secure.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
In general, you can browse our website without giving us any personal
information. We use Web-tracking software to analyze traffic to this website in
order to understand our customers' and visitors' needs and to continually
improve our site for them. This Web tracking software collects only anonymous,
aggregate statistics.
However, certain activities on our site may require you to provide personal
information. For example you need to provide this information to submit a
unique proposal idea or to contact us.
Disclosure of Personal
Information
We do not sell or otherwise provide your personal information to third parties
for any reason, except as required by law.
Children and Privacy
Our website does not offer information intended to attract children. IceStore
does not knowingly solicit personal information from minors.
Security of Personal Information
We have implemented industry-standard security mechanisms and procedures to
protect data from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration,
and destruction when you submit any form on icestore.com
Links to Other Websites
Our website contains links to information on other websites. We do not have any
control over these other websites, and therefore we cannot be responsible for
the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting
those sites. Those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and if you
have questions about how a site uses your information, consult that site's
privacy statement.
Unsubscribing or Changing Your Account Information
If you have subscribed to receive email correspondence from IceStore, you may
change your preferences or unsubscribe at any time by following the
instructions provided in the emails.
Your Consent
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of the information
you provide to us as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We may change this
Privacy Policy from time to time and without notice. If we change our Privacy
Policy, we will publish those changes on this page. If users have any questions
or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:
Since
2001, IceStore offers the very highest quality GIA certified loose diamonds, yellow diamonds and fine jewelry at a fraction of the cost of traditional retail. Compare us to Tiffany & Co, Cartier, Harry Winston and get the same or better quality at a fraction of the price.
We are
dedicated to making this your most comfortable diamond and jewelry shopping experience ever.
Contact Info
Beverly Hills, CA.
